[{
        "question": "Which organ belongs to the Digestive System:",
        "options": ["Thymus", "Stomach", "Heart", "Trachea"],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Adults have fewer bones than babies do.",
        "options": ["true", "false"],
        "answer": 0,
        "description": "Lots of bones start out as several fragments at birth,then fuse together into a single bone later in life"
    },
    {
        "question": "Our human body has.........",
        "options": ["206 bones", "210 bones", "306 bones", "706 bones"],
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Your fingernails and hair keep growing after you die.",
        "options": ["true", "false"],
        "answer": 1,
        "description": "They really don't"
    },
    {
        "question": "One important function of bones is to produce.",
        "options": ["tendons", "ligaments", "blood cells", "cartilage"],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following has become the first country to make all forms of public transport free?",
        "options": ["Monaco", "Liechtenstein", "Luxembourg", "Andorra"],
        "answer": 2,
        "description": "Luxembourg in Europe has become the first country to make all forms of public transport free. It is the second smallest country in the European Union"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following has become the first country to make all forms of public transport free?",
        "options": ["Monaco", "India", "Japan", "Singapore"],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is to host Commonwealth shooting, archery events in 2022?",
        "options": ["Australia", "India", "Brunei", "Cameroon"],
        "answer": 3,
        "description": "India to host Commonwealth shooting, archery events at Chandigarh in January 2022"
    },
    {
        "question": "26 The International Criminal Police Organisation (INTERPOL) has its headquarters at",
        "options": ["Montreal", "Bonn", "Paris", "London"],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "30 Where is the headquarters of Botanical Survey of India located?",
        "options": ["Kolkata", "Lucknow", "Ootacmund", "Darjeeling"],
        "answer": 0
    }
]